So for the question of where to store the background color information.
بالنسبة للسؤال عن مكان تخزين معلومات لون الخلفية.
We could have stored the background color in the Word object.
يمكننا تخزين لون الخلفية في كائن النص.
So that means for all number words
وبالنسبة لجميع نصوص الأرقام
we could pass in the orange color as an input in the constructor.
يمكننا إدخالها باللون البرتقالي كمدخل في الملائم.
But that would be a lot of wasted memory because we're remembering the same color
يعد ذلك استهلاكًا أكبر من الذاكرة لأننا نتذكر اللون ذاته
for all the words in the same category.
لجميع الكلمات في نفس الفئة.
If we want to reduce the amount of repeated information in our app,
إذا كنا نرغب في تقليل معدل المعلومات المكررة في تطبيقنا،
the more appropriate place is to store the color information
فإن المكان الأنسب هو تخزين معلومات اللون
in the WordAdapter class.
في فئة موائم النص.
So each activity has its own list view and WordAdapter.
ولكل نشاط واجهة القائمة الخاصة به وموائم النص.
So for each WordAdapter, we can store a color inside it,
وبالنسبة لكل موائم نص، يمكننا تخزين لون داخله،
according to the category it was created for.
طبقًا للفئة التي تم إنشاؤها من أجلها.
So as I wrote here, we can store the background color information in
كما أوضح هنا، يمكننا تخزين معلومات لون الخلفية في
the WordAdapter, so every time a new WordAdapter object is created for
موائم النص، حيث يتم إنشاء كائن موائم نص جديد
a certain list, it will apply the same background color to all list items.
لقائمة محددة، وسيطبق لون الخلفية ذاتها لجميع عناصر القائمة.
So following this logic,
وعليك اتباع هذا المنطق،
the WordAdapter in the numbers activity would store the orange color.
ويتم تخزين موائم النص في نشاط الأرقام في اللون البرتقالي.
The WordAdapter in the family activity would hold the green color and so on.
ويحمل موائم النص في نشاط العائلة في اللون الأخضر وهكذا.
Well, you may be wondering why don't we just store it in the activity then?
قد تتساءل عن سبب عدم تخزيننا له في النشاط.
Because each activity has a different color.
لأن كل نشاط له لون مختلف.
Well, the activity does need to know the color but
يجب أن يحدد النشاط اللون لكن
only when we initialize the WordAdapter.
فقط عند كتابة موائم النص بحروف كبيرة.
So ultimately,
وفي النهاية،
the WordAdapter has to store the color as a global variable so that it can
يجب على موائم النص تخزين اللون كمتغير عام حتى يمكن
keep referring back to the color every time it creates a new list item layout.
الرجوع إلى اللون في كل مرة يتم فيها إنشاء مخطط عناصر قائمة جديدة.